{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004104262","data":{"timestamp":" 947004104262"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004111074","data":{"timestamp":" 947004111074"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004117362","data":{"timestamp":" 947004117362"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004126544","data":{"timestamp":" 947004126544"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 736892d0-5110-4f42-aef2-85e285356c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004131737","data":{"timestamp":" 947004131737"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 736892d0-5110-4f42-aef2-85e285356c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004142054","data":{"timestamp":" 947004142054"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 736892d0-5110-4f42-aef2-85e285356c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004149402","data":{"timestamp":" 947004149402"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 736892d0-5110-4f42-aef2-85e285356c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_9-8"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004151945","data":{"timestamp":" 947004151945"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 736892d0-5110-4f42-aef2-85e285356c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_8_9-8"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004159870","data":{"timestamp":" 947004159869"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 736892d0-5110-4f42-aef2-85e285356c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_8_9-8"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004166807","data":{"timestamp":" 947004166807"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 736892d0-5110-4f42-aef2-85e285356c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_8_9-8"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004177579","data":{"timestamp":" 947004177579"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 736892d0-5110-4f42-aef2-85e285356c9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_8_9-8"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004189176","data":{"timestamp":" 947004189176"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 5ec3d7ad-7cff-443a-8f06-a1433f0a3967"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004194264","data":{"timestamp":" 947004194264"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 5ec3d7ad-7cff-443a-8f06-a1433f0a3967"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004199387","data":{"timestamp":" 947004199387"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 5ec3d7ad-7cff-443a-8f06-a1433f0a3967"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_7-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004203675","data":{"timestamp":" 947004203675"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 5ec3d7ad-7cff-443a-8f06-a1433f0a3967"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004218279","data":{"timestamp":" 947004218278"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 5ec3d7ad-7cff-443a-8f06-a1433f0a3967"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_2-0"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004222959","data":{"timestamp":" 947004222959"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 5ec3d7ad-7cff-443a-8f06-a1433f0a3967"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-1"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004227691","data":{"timestamp":" 947004227691"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 5ec3d7ad-7cff-443a-8f06-a1433f0a3967"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004232262","data":{"timestamp":" 947004232262"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 5ec3d7ad-7cff-443a-8f06-a1433f0a3967"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_6-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004236449","data":{"timestamp":" 947004236449"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 5ec3d7ad-7cff-443a-8f06-a1433f0a3967"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004242058","data":{"timestamp":" 947004242058"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 5ec3d7ad-7cff-443a-8f06-a1433f0a3967"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004248742","data":{"timestamp":" 947004248741"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 5ec3d7ad-7cff-443a-8f06-a1433f0a3967"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004258570","data":{"timestamp":" 947004258569"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 3169b520-a1f7-477f-92f4-430175727f02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004263012","data":{"timestamp":" 947004263011"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 3169b520-a1f7-477f-92f4-430175727f02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_2-0"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004267589","data":{"timestamp":" 947004267589"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 3169b520-a1f7-477f-92f4-430175727f02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_7-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004272925","data":{"timestamp":" 947004272925"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 3169b520-a1f7-477f-92f4-430175727f02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004277376","data":{"timestamp":" 947004277376"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 3169b520-a1f7-477f-92f4-430175727f02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004281818","data":{"timestamp":" 947004281818"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 3169b520-a1f7-477f-92f4-430175727f02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004286439","data":{"timestamp":" 947004286439"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 3169b520-a1f7-477f-92f4-430175727f02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_6-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004291453","data":{"timestamp":" 947004291452"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 3169b520-a1f7-477f-92f4-430175727f02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004296261","data":{"timestamp":" 947004296261"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 3169b520-a1f7-477f-92f4-430175727f02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004300738","data":{"timestamp":" 947004300738"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 3169b520-a1f7-477f-92f4-430175727f02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004307317","data":{"timestamp":" 947004307314"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 3169b520-a1f7-477f-92f4-430175727f02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004340304","data":{"timestamp":" 947004340304"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004349955","data":{"timestamp":" 947004349955"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_B"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004359626","data":{"timestamp":" 947004359626"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_B"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004369884","data":{"timestamp":" 947004369884"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" C"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004373520","data":{"timestamp":" 947004373520"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004383865","data":{"timestamp":" 947004383865"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004391670","data":{"timestamp":" 947004391670"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004410232","data":{"timestamp":" 947004410232"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004423053","data":{"timestamp":" 947004423053"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004434742","data":{"timestamp":" 947004434742"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_F"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004447321","data":{"timestamp":" 947004447321"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_G"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004459434","data":{"timestamp":" 947004459434"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_H"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004469506","data":{"timestamp":" 947004469506"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_I"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004479452","data":{"timestamp":" 947004479452"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004490972","data":{"timestamp":" 947004490972"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004500317","data":{"timestamp":" 947004500317"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004512720","data":{"timestamp":" 947004512720"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_M"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004524423","data":{"timestamp":" 947004524423"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_N"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004534734","data":{"timestamp":" 947004534734"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004544064","data":{"timestamp":" 947004544064"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_P"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004560268","data":{"timestamp":" 947004560268"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_R"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004569567","data":{"timestamp":" 947004569567"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004588429","data":{"timestamp":" 947004588429"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004600955","data":{"timestamp":" 947004600955"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004610826","data":{"timestamp":" 947004610826"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_V"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004627621","data":{"timestamp":" 947004627621"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_W"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004641647","data":{"timestamp":" 947004641647"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004657338","data":{"timestamp":" 947004657338"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004667574","data":{"timestamp":" 947004667573"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 52ae7482-593a-4a05-86b2-6b0d63a4a797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004677289","data":{"timestamp":" 947004677289"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" c98157b4-a28c-4c0a-85ca-5c2042b2d89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004677519","data":{"timestamp":" 947004677519"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" c98157b4-a28c-4c0a-85ca-5c2042b2d89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004678483","data":{"timestamp":" 947004678482"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" c98157b4-a28c-4c0a-85ca-5c2042b2d89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004678793","data":{"timestamp":" 947004678792"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" c98157b4-a28c-4c0a-85ca-5c2042b2d89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_20"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004678878","data":{"timestamp":" 947004678878"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" c98157b4-a28c-4c0a-85ca-5c2042b2d89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004693714","data":{"timestamp":" 947004693714"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" c98157b4-a28c-4c0a-85ca-5c2042b2d89a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_20"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004717812","data":{"timestamp":" 947004717812"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004718289","data":{"timestamp":" 947004718289"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004718978","data":{"timestamp":" 947004718978"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004719200","data":{"timestamp":" 947004719200"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004719430","data":{"timestamp":" 947004719430"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004719651","data":{"timestamp":" 947004719651"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004719838","data":{"timestamp":" 947004719838"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004724290","data":{"timestamp":" 947004724290"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004729108","data":{"timestamp":" 947004729108"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004733338","data":{"timestamp":" 947004733338"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004734530","data":{"timestamp":" 947004734530"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004738531","data":{"timestamp":" 947004738531"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004738769","data":{"timestamp":" 947004738769"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004738973","data":{"timestamp":" 947004738973"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004739186","data":{"timestamp":" 947004739186"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004739399","data":{"timestamp":" 947004739399"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004739612","data":{"timestamp":" 947004739612"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004739790","data":{"timestamp":" 947004739790"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004739969","data":{"timestamp":" 947004739969"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004742753","data":{"timestamp":" 947004742752"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004743000","data":{"timestamp":" 947004743000"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004743187","data":{"timestamp":" 947004743187"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004743376","data":{"timestamp":" 947004743375"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004743580","data":{"timestamp":" 947004743580"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004743758","data":{"timestamp":" 947004743757"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004743970","data":{"timestamp":" 947004743970"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004744175","data":{"timestamp":" 947004744175"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004744370","data":{"timestamp":" 947004744370"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004744583","data":{"timestamp":" 947004744583"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004744788","data":{"timestamp":" 947004744788"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004744983","data":{"timestamp":" 947004744983"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004747264","data":{"timestamp":" 947004747264"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004747494","data":{"timestamp":" 947004747494"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004747707","data":{"timestamp":" 947004747707"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004747920","data":{"timestamp":" 947004747920"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004748116","data":{"timestamp":" 947004748115"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004748320","data":{"timestamp":" 947004748320"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004748524","data":{"timestamp":" 947004748524"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004748754","data":{"timestamp":" 947004748754"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004748950","data":{"timestamp":" 947004748950"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004765134","data":{"timestamp":" 947004765134"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004765372","data":{"timestamp":" 947004765372"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004765610","data":{"timestamp":" 947004765610"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004770845","data":{"timestamp":" 947004770845"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004771032","data":{"timestamp":" 947004771032"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004771254","data":{"timestamp":" 947004771253"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004771467","data":{"timestamp":" 947004771467"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004771679","data":{"timestamp":" 947004771679"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004771901","data":{"timestamp":" 947004771900"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004772105","data":{"timestamp":" 947004772105"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004772327","data":{"timestamp":" 947004772327"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004772548","data":{"timestamp":" 947004772548"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004772744","data":{"timestamp":" 947004772744"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004772990","data":{"timestamp":" 947004772990"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004774335","data":{"timestamp":" 947004774335"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004774582","data":{"timestamp":" 947004774582"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004774787","data":{"timestamp":" 947004774786"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004774982","data":{"timestamp":" 947004774982"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004775229","data":{"timestamp":" 947004775229"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004775442","data":{"timestamp":" 947004775442"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004775672","data":{"timestamp":" 947004775672"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004775876","data":{"timestamp":" 947004775876"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004778745","data":{"timestamp":" 947004778745"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004778983","data":{"timestamp":" 947004778983"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004779630","data":{"timestamp":" 947004779630"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004779852","data":{"timestamp":" 947004779852"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004780056","data":{"timestamp":" 947004780056"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004780294","data":{"timestamp":" 947004780294"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004780482","data":{"timestamp":" 947004780481"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004780703","data":{"timestamp":" 947004780703"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004781145","data":{"timestamp":" 947004781145"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004781362","data":{"timestamp":" 947004781362"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004781537","data":{"timestamp":" 947004781537"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004782012","data":{"timestamp":" 947004782012"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004794054","data":{"timestamp":" 947004794053"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004800669","data":{"timestamp":" 947004800668"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004816561","data":{"timestamp":" 947004816561"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" e9ba0e93-1898-4ccc-bc38-c470e25bf63a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004827683","data":{"timestamp":" 947004827683"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2e57d0ce-d1d7-4e5b-b230-504f2b437edb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004833286","data":{"timestamp":" 947004833286"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2e57d0ce-d1d7-4e5b-b230-504f2b437edb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-3-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004838746","data":{"timestamp":" 947004838746"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2e57d0ce-d1d7-4e5b-b230-504f2b437edb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-9-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004844401","data":{"timestamp":" 947004844401"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2e57d0ce-d1d7-4e5b-b230-504f2b437edb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-9-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004852487","data":{"timestamp":" 947004852487"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2e57d0ce-d1d7-4e5b-b230-504f2b437edb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_2-0-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004858124","data":{"timestamp":" 947004858124"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2e57d0ce-d1d7-4e5b-b230-504f2b437edb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_2-0-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004878829","data":{"timestamp":" 947004878829"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2e57d0ce-d1d7-4e5b-b230-504f2b437edb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_7-8-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004884535","data":{"timestamp":" 947004884534"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2e57d0ce-d1d7-4e5b-b230-504f2b437edb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_7-8-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004889209","data":{"timestamp":" 947004889209"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2e57d0ce-d1d7-4e5b-b230-504f2b437edb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004895702","data":{"timestamp":" 947004895702"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2e57d0ce-d1d7-4e5b-b230-504f2b437edb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004900513","data":{"timestamp":" 947004900513"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2e57d0ce-d1d7-4e5b-b230-504f2b437edb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-2-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004907414","data":{"timestamp":" 947004907414"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2e57d0ce-d1d7-4e5b-b230-504f2b437edb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_9-7-8"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004912448","data":{"timestamp":" 947004912448"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2e57d0ce-d1d7-4e5b-b230-504f2b437edb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004919016","data":{"timestamp":" 947004919015"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2e57d0ce-d1d7-4e5b-b230-504f2b437edb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004942742","data":{"timestamp":" 947004942741"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2e57d0ce-d1d7-4e5b-b230-504f2b437edb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004948432","data":{"timestamp":" 947004948431"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2e57d0ce-d1d7-4e5b-b230-504f2b437edb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004958006","data":{"timestamp":" 947004958006"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004961809","data":{"timestamp":" 947004961809"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004966077","data":{"timestamp":" 947004966076"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004971511","data":{"timestamp":" 947004971511"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004975408","data":{"timestamp":" 947004975408"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004979026","data":{"timestamp":" 947004979026"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004984283","data":{"timestamp":" 947004984282"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004987645","data":{"timestamp":" 947004987645"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004990879","data":{"timestamp":" 947004990878"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004994189","data":{"timestamp":" 947004994189"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947004997646","data":{"timestamp":" 947004997646"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005000709","data":{"timestamp":" 947005000709"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005003643","data":{"timestamp":" 947005003643"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005007109","data":{"timestamp":" 947005007109"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005010600","data":{"timestamp":" 947005010600"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005015343","data":{"timestamp":" 947005015343"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005018382","data":{"timestamp":" 947005018382"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005021907","data":{"timestamp":" 947005021906"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005025010","data":{"timestamp":" 947005025010"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005028493","data":{"timestamp":" 947005028493"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005031316","data":{"timestamp":" 947005031316"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005034294","data":{"timestamp":" 947005034294"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005037410","data":{"timestamp":" 947005037409"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005040643","data":{"timestamp":" 947005040643"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005046434","data":{"timestamp":" 947005046433"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ebfcaf81-d07e-499e-a3aa-5de73ab7f783"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005070700","data":{"timestamp":" 947005070700"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2f96e85c-a00e-46df-9d0e-7241a24438b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-9-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005075146","data":{"timestamp":" 947005075146"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2f96e85c-a00e-46df-9d0e-7241a24438b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-2-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005079387","data":{"timestamp":" 947005079387"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2f96e85c-a00e-46df-9d0e-7241a24438b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005085112","data":{"timestamp":" 947005085112"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2f96e85c-a00e-46df-9d0e-7241a24438b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005089875","data":{"timestamp":" 947005089875"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2f96e85c-a00e-46df-9d0e-7241a24438b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-3-2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005095371","data":{"timestamp":" 947005095371"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2f96e85c-a00e-46df-9d0e-7241a24438b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_9-7-8"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005102764","data":{"timestamp":" 947005102764"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2f96e85c-a00e-46df-9d0e-7241a24438b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_2-0-1"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005108260","data":{"timestamp":" 947005108260"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2f96e85c-a00e-46df-9d0e-7241a24438b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-10"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005117659","data":{"timestamp":" 947005117659"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2f96e85c-a00e-46df-9d0e-7241a24438b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005126177","data":{"timestamp":" 947005126177"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2f96e85c-a00e-46df-9d0e-7241a24438b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_7-8-6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005131837","data":{"timestamp":" 947005131837"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2f96e85c-a00e-46df-9d0e-7241a24438b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_7-8-6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005141889","data":{"timestamp":" 947005141889"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2f96e85c-a00e-46df-9d0e-7241a24438b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005148683","data":{"timestamp":" 947005148681"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2f96e85c-a00e-46df-9d0e-7241a24438b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005165372","data":{"timestamp":" 947005165371"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2f96e85c-a00e-46df-9d0e-7241a24438b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005173270","data":{"timestamp":" 947005173268"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 2f96e85c-a00e-46df-9d0e-7241a24438b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005183984","data":{"timestamp":" 947005183984"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005187791","data":{"timestamp":" 947005187790"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005191247","data":{"timestamp":" 947005191247"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005194271","data":{"timestamp":" 947005194271"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005198200","data":{"timestamp":" 947005198199"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005202288","data":{"timestamp":" 947005202287"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005207905","data":{"timestamp":" 947005207904"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005213383","data":{"timestamp":" 947005213383"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005217341","data":{"timestamp":" 947005217341"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005221455","data":{"timestamp":" 947005221455"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005227592","data":{"timestamp":" 947005227592"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005231611","data":{"timestamp":" 947005231611"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005235411","data":{"timestamp":" 947005235411"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005239951","data":{"timestamp":" 947005239950"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005245881","data":{"timestamp":" 947005245881"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005249605","data":{"timestamp":" 947005249605"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005252497","data":{"timestamp":" 947005252497"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005255588","data":{"timestamp":" 947005255587"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005268585","data":{"timestamp":" 947005268584"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005274859","data":{"timestamp":" 947005274859"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005283893","data":{"timestamp":" 947005283893"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005289642","data":{"timestamp":" 947005289642"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005294285","data":{"timestamp":" 947005294284"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005310468","data":{"timestamp":" 947005310467"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005314027","data":{"timestamp":" 947005314027"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005319856","data":{"timestamp":" 947005319856"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" d4166a56-8ca2-4745-bd89-7b7df0b8e9f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005331606","data":{"timestamp":" 947005331606"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ef18f015-ce2f-45cb-8b11-ccf851613154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-2-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005336174","data":{"timestamp":" 947005336174"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ef18f015-ce2f-45cb-8b11-ccf851613154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-5-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005342093","data":{"timestamp":" 947005342093"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ef18f015-ce2f-45cb-8b11-ccf851613154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-5-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005346824","data":{"timestamp":" 947005346824"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ef18f015-ce2f-45cb-8b11-ccf851613154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_0-8-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005351339","data":{"timestamp":" 947005351338"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ef18f015-ce2f-45cb-8b11-ccf851613154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_0-7-2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005355799","data":{"timestamp":" 947005355799"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ef18f015-ce2f-45cb-8b11-ccf851613154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_3-9-2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005361688","data":{"timestamp":" 947005361688"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ef18f015-ce2f-45cb-8b11-ccf851613154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-2-6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005367422","data":{"timestamp":" 947005367422"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ef18f015-ce2f-45cb-8b11-ccf851613154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-3-5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005373244","data":{"timestamp":" 947005373244"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ef18f015-ce2f-45cb-8b11-ccf851613154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-4-2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005378372","data":{"timestamp":" 947005378372"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ef18f015-ce2f-45cb-8b11-ccf851613154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005383468","data":{"timestamp":" 947005383468"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ef18f015-ce2f-45cb-8b11-ccf851613154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_6-7-2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005390322","data":{"timestamp":" 947005390321"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ef18f015-ce2f-45cb-8b11-ccf851613154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_7_6-7-2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005408508","data":{"timestamp":" 947005408508"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" ef18f015-ce2f-45cb-8b11-ccf851613154"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_6-7-2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005419373","data":{"timestamp":" 947005419373"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 8d3c1239-78c7-4174-aa9f-ea11d2c61871"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005419957","data":{"timestamp":" 947005419956"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 8d3c1239-78c7-4174-aa9f-ea11d2c61871"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005420151","data":{"timestamp":" 947005420151"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 8d3c1239-78c7-4174-aa9f-ea11d2c61871"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005420474","data":{"timestamp":" 947005420473"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 8d3c1239-78c7-4174-aa9f-ea11d2c61871"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005420593","data":{"timestamp":" 947005420593"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 8d3c1239-78c7-4174-aa9f-ea11d2c61871"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005435129","data":{"timestamp":" 947005435129"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 8d3c1239-78c7-4174-aa9f-ea11d2c61871"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005440828","data":{"timestamp":" 947005440828"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 8d3c1239-78c7-4174-aa9f-ea11d2c61871"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005449791","data":{"timestamp":" 947005449791"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 8d3c1239-78c7-4174-aa9f-ea11d2c61871"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005456313","data":{"timestamp":" 947005456313"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 8d3c1239-78c7-4174-aa9f-ea11d2c61871"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947005464625","data":{"timestamp":" 947005464625"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_194130"," gameId":" 8d3c1239-78c7-4174-aa9f-ea11d2c61871"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}